After our battle with the Frog
Fiends, we headed back to the village.
Luckily, we didn't run into any issues on
the return trip, but when we got there…
The village!
I'm sorry everybody, I
know that you're tired,
but it seems we have one
more matter to take care of.
Munami and Mrs.
I understand how she feels.
And she's known them for
a lot longer than I have.
There has to be some way I can help her.
Look forward, please insert coins.
What was that?
Thank you, forward there.
Please insert coins.
Look forward, please insert coins!
I think I get it.
I should look forward.
Yeah, you're right!
I can't just sit here and do nothing!
It's not supposed to be a lie.
Looks like something got
dragged through here.
But what?
How could something like this happen?
Is the inn okay?
It's destroyed.
Oh, no.
Hey, Mrs! Murder me! Ah, crap.
At this rate, she'll run inside.
You could too bad.
What's that mean?
Sorry about that.
You're telling me to calm down.
They would have responded
if they were here,
which means they evacuated somewhere else.
Hello there.
There's only one place they'd
go at a time like this.
Yeah, I know just the place.
Hey, Llamas and Boxo.
Karios, Garth.
Glad to see you guys made it
back safely. We've been busy.
Yeah, about that.
I saw the inn.
Now, before you go asking,
they're both all right.
Oh, what a relief.
This is where the transfer circle is.
It's the safest place.
Of course.
The village was built inside of a dungeon.
It's only natural for it
to have all these defenses.
It's Lamy!
I thought I heard your voice.
You're okay.
I was worried.
We had quite the exciting
time while you were gone.
Did you guys finish the request?
Yep.
It was a piece of cake.
Thank you very much.
I recognize so many faces around me.
I've only lived here a few weeks now.
But I don't want to lose any of them as
someone who's already died once I can't help
but feel That way all
goods are on me today
come and get it
I
soon came to find out
that this two-headed Snake monster is
apparently a natural predator of the frogmen
all the fat makes the meat taste Super
yummy whoa they eat the
monsters they kill I
guess when you live in a dungeon you've
got to be Pretty wild I I mean resilient it
seems I managed to attract a couple new
customers with today's
free Giveaway the alcoholic
drink I just stocked is selling like crazy
along with the potato chips And odin enjoy
the free stuff while you can because after
tomorrow I'm gonna earn tons of money?
Come back, Poxo!
Hey, you okay out here?
I got to experience so many new things
since we went on that expedition.
That alone made it all worth it.
Hello there.
You know what?
Right now, I'm so grateful.
Even though half the village was
destroyed, everything turned out A-OK.
And that's not all.
I'm relieved that you
found your place here.
Did you see how long that line was?
I was afraid they wouldn't like you.
But then, before I knew it, you
became friends with everybody. Yay!
So, I was worried for nothing.
I'm so happy.
She was worried about my well-being?
She really is a good person.
Sleep well, Lamas.
Here's to tomorrow.
The merchants are always busy in the
morning getting their shops ready.
As expected, there are lots of carpenters
as well as hunters on guard duty.
And everyone's got to eat, right?
Director Bear sent summons for Lamas.
I'm not sure why, but I hope it's to
reward her for the successful expedition.
Good news, Boxo!
The director asked me to personally
help out with a special request!
Isn't that great?
Hello there! Uh-huh!
I'll be cleaning up rumble around town!
I should have guessed.
Munami!
Missus!
I'm here to help you out.
Your blessing is gonna
come in handy for sure.
We'll be relying on you then.
Hello there.
Is this where we were assigned?
Oh, there's the box with
the mind of its own.
That's great. Lucky us.
And the pay is good.
We'll buy a whole bunch of stuff.
The cart's all full.
I'll be right back.
Because of her blessing,
Lamas gained a reputation
of being a screw-up,
so her fellow hunters
treated her like a nuisance.
Perhaps if she'd been
given more jobs like this,
they would have seen the
upsides of her blessing.
There you are, Lamas.
Looks like you're hard at work, huh?
I figured you youngsters might be hungry
after looking around all this junk.
Choose whatever you'd like from Boxo.
It's on me.
Oh, naturally that goes
for you ladies as well.
Well, if you're fine, then I'll have
one of these and one of those, too!
Remember, Lamy, at times like this, you
should pick the most expensive things.
Since you so generously offered, why
don't we start with a hundred soups?
Wait, let's be reasonable here.
The truth is, I wanted to ask
if you would join our party.
Hmm?
That goes for Boxo, too, of course.
Nope, thank you, though.
Okay, then.
Why in the world would you say no?
That was an invitation to
join the Menagerie of Fools!
Because we need all the help we
can get rebuilding the village.
I can't run off like that
before the repairs are done.
Would you be Mr.
Boxo, the strange magic
artifact with a mind of its own?
Hello there.
I suppose that phrase is
your way of saying yes.
Hey, Boxo, I'm back now.
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to
interrupt you. It's fine.
I'm Mokoe from the Exchange House.
This man is my assistant.
His name's Gokai.
It's a pleasure to meet the two of you.
Truth is,
we received word that this stratum
was running low on silver coins,
so we came to investigate the cause.
Seems someone out there
is hoarding silver coins.
Disgraceful.
Oh, that's because everyone
pays Boxo in silver!
Don't tell them that!
That's what I suspected.
Since that's the case, I
have a proposal for you.
We've brought along nearly a
hundred gold coins with us.
Would you mind exchanging
them for your silver coins?
Gold coins?
If I remember right, each
is worth a hundred silver.
When you convert it to yen, I'd
say it's about a hundred thousand.
That's a ton of money.
What do you say? Too bad.
Are you saying you don't accept the offer?
It's not that I don't want to do it,
but I don't have any way of
exchanging currencies right now.
Ooh, maybe if you buy something with a
gold coin, you can get silver's exchange.
Ho, ho, ho!
This is the first gold coin I've accepted.
I think this may actually work out.
Let's keep buying more items.
Finally, I got put through the
damn ringer thanks to that jerk.
If we continue on, we might
start to interfere with Mr.
Boxer's business.
Let's stop for today.
We still have more coins, but
we'll exchange them next time.
I look forward to working with you again.
Amazing.
You gotta be the richest
box thingy in town.
You better be careful to not get robbed.
Hello there.
You could even win a reward.
Yeah, come on.
Come to papa.
Seven. Seven.
Six.
Ah, so close.
Too bad.
It took a while,
but I'm finally able to use this
particular phrase for its intended purpose.
I added the digital lottery function.
Ever since I installed it,
I've increased sales by 30%.
Gotta relax.
Just calm down.
This will be the last one, I swear.
No matter what, I'm
bound to win something.
I can feel it.
I'd even wager this old life
of mine on this final shot.
What the heck are you going on
about this time, you old fool?
That bad habit of yours
is rearing its ugly head.
Knowing you, I bet you don't
remember what day today is.
Of course I do. I remember. I promise.
Sorry, Boxo.
I sent a letter to Hulemy,
but she hasn't responded yet.
She's probably wandering
around a stratum somewhere.
So, could you keep waiting
here for a little longer?
Hello there.
Are you too busy right now? Director!
I'd like to have a chat with you.
Could you visit the Hunter Association?
I mentioned this to you before.
You both performed well
during the expedition.
Without your quick thinking,
there's a high probability the situation
would have gone from bad to worse.
I'm grateful.
By the way, I have a small
favor I'd like to ask you, Boxo.
So, would you mind giving
us a bit of privacy?
All right.
I suppose I'll just wait downstairs, then.
Thank you.
I'll send for you as soon
as our business is done.
Okay.
Recently, a large number of people have
been hoping to migrate to the village.
But increasing the population
brings a number of issues.
One of which is food, but you
can help alleviate any shortages.
That said, there are other concerns.
Hygiene being particularly difficult.
We bear fiends don't
have many physical needs.
Outside of mating season, of course.
It's a shame humans aren't so simple.
They're susceptible to
things like diseases.
which could delay reconstruction efforts.
I see.
This is kind of a sensitive
subject, so he had Lamas leave.
But hey, as a former human
myself, it's just natural.
Why don't you come inside, Shirley?
My name is Shirley.
It's lovely to meet you.
Oh, she's so pretty.
Ideally, allowing more people to live
in the village would be a good thing.
But as the population grows,
we have to tighten health regulations,
which can then create more
problems down the road.
I've got something in mind
for preventing diseases,
but the question is, will
they be able to understand it?
Well, I might as well show it to them.
Oh, how intriguing.
So this is how you go about
changing the products you sell.
What's inside this package?
Is this how you plan to
stop the spread of disease?
Hello there.
Ten silver coins.
It certainly doesn't come cheap.
Looks like there are notches all around
the edges to make opening the bag easier.
How convenient. Hello there.
This material.
I've never seen anything like it before.
It's interesting how it
stretches and contracts.
What's more, there's some
kind of slimy liquid inside.
I'm not doing anything wrong, but
somehow this feels kind of immoral.
How are we supposed to use this thing?
Hold on, it looks like there's
a piece of paper in the box.
Well, let's see what it says.
Ah, so that's how it works.
It's surprisingly simple.
Thank goodness for these diagrams.
This is a truly ingenious
product, Mr. Boxo.
It will protect against diseases.
We should buy them in bulk and hand
them out in the entertainment quarter.
Whew, more happy customers.
Boxo, did something happen?
It feels like you're lighter than usual.
I've got a regular who
comes by in the afternoon.
I've been trying to overlook
her little fits of mischief.
But that ends today!
Please insert coins.
How dare you!
Do you have any idea who
I am, you wretched box?
Bring that thing apart! Listen to me!
Oh, Miss Gracious, Miss Suori's antics
have been getting out of hand lately.
As usual, the little girl showed up again.
Father, you promised me that
you'd come home today. Liar.
Hello there.
You're saying this is for me?
Thank you very much.
Alright then.
Thank you, I guess.
I look forward to serving you again.
Whoa!
I wish I had your figure, Shirley.
I'm so jealous.
You flatter me.
I can't move on my own, so it's not
my fault they decided to put me here.
But boy, am I glad I'm a vending machine.
Boxo!
Could I get the usual?
Thanks, I can't get enough
of this liquid hair soap.
Every time I use it, it makes
my hair feel glossy and clean.
Yep, that's why I've been installed here.
I definitely didn't stock up on these
products just so I'd be brought in.
No Suori.
There's more?
I've been shedding like crazy lately.
Isn't it because your
new coat's growing in?
Yeah, on top of that, I'm aching all over.
Ah, right, it's almost mating season.
Boxo's here today.
Guess I'll stock up on fur wash.
Good idea.
I'll use this to make
my coat look amazing,
and then all the males
will pay attention to me.
Not only that, but it makes
your scent irresistible.
One whiff and my boyfriend
got all hot and bothered,
even though it wasn't mating season.
Seriously?
Only in the bathhouse.
Looks like that hands-on-hip pose is so
universal, they even do it in other worlds.
Ah!
A cold one after a hot bath?
What more can you ask for?
That sounds lovely.
Could I please have one too, Boxo?
I think I'll go with
the brown drink today.
It's got the perfect amount of sweetness.
Sure enough.
After a bath, it's got to be
fruit or coffee-flavored milk.
Straight from the bottle, of course.
It's a bathhouse special.
Hey, Grandpa, what do these numbers mean?
They change whenever you buy something.
If you're lucky and the numbers end up the
same, you can get another item for free.
People say if you're
lucky enough to win here,
then happiness will follow
you for the rest of the day.
That sounds fun!
I want to try, Grandpa!
All right, let's give it a go.
Let's see, why don't we
start you off with a water?
Yeah, that sounds good!
I'm glad I worked up the nerve to return.
And I'm sorry for being
such a bad daughter.
You were right, Mom.
As long as you're safe.
That's all I care about.
I'm happy that you've come home, dear.
Hooray!
I only need one more number to match!
Not so fast.
The last one's the hardest.
Seven! Seven! Seven! Seven!
I got a seven!
I did it!
How come I'm never that lucky?
Hurry up and make your decision, May.
Otherwise, you might run out
of time to get your free item.
Hey, with that!
Here, this is for you, Grandpa.
What's this?
You're giving your prize to me?
My goodness, you don't have to do that.
It's too bad the day's almost over.
It'll only make you
happy for a short while.
How unlucky.
Unlucky?
But, Grandpa, I've been feeling happy
all day because I'm with you and Grandpa.
The rumor about the prize was true.
You're right.
Was it a coincidence that little
May hit the jackpot just now?
It's the best.
Well, some things are better left unsaid.
Boxxo,
I heard that you can use an ability called
mimicry to blend in
with your surroundings.
Is that true?
Hello there!
Wow, that's quite the handy skill.
I bet you could sit right there with it
active and no one would ever notice you.
Now that I've confirmed your ability, I
have a request I'd like to ask of you.
Me?
I'd like you to stake out
the area where a number of
crimes have taken place so you
can identify the perpetrator.
But before we begin the operation,
I'd like to see more of your mimicry.
This spot's perfect.
I've got a clear view of
the Hunters Association.
Not bad.
Boxo!
Where do you go?
Didn't the director say he
was borrowing him for a bit?
Oh, I forgot.
Do you have any plans?
You want to help around here again?
I was going to help out around
the Hunters Association today
so I can meet up with Boxo
whenever he's ready to come back.
All right, all right.
Hello, Lamas.
That's a rare sight.
Boxo isn't with you?
Nope.
Turns out he's helping
out the director today.
Is that so? That's too bad.
He's so popular.
Must be nice.
Ah, what a nice, peaceful day.
Oh, I was looking forward
to some fruit juice.
Boxo's a big, dumb, stupid jerk.
Don't say that, Swari.
If you can't say anything nice,
you shouldn't say it at all.
Look who it is, the booby monster.
Hey, cut it out.
I told you before, it's Lammis.
Whatever, Lammeries.
Have you given any more
thought to my offer?
My name is Lammis, and you
should just give up on that.
I'm never going to give you Boxo.
With the amount I'm offering,
your family could
further it away for three
generations and still
not run out of money.
Like I said, Boxo isn't my
property, so he's not mine to sell.
Besides, money alone would
never be enough to replace him.
You act like you're his friend, but
you want to keep Boxxo all to yourself,
don't you?
Come on, think about it.
Wouldn't he be much
happier spending the rest
of his life with me and
my family's magnificent
residence instead of wasting
his time getting lugged
around by some stumpy
woman with no sex appeal?
I'm a stumpy woman with no sex appeal?
You know, that's rich
coming from you, Suori.
That's not fair.
I'm still growing.
I have plenty to look forward to.
I'll have you know Mother has
even bigger ones than yours.
Oh, no, poor Miss Suori.
She has no idea that the
Madam's been patting her bodies.
Well, we can lay this issue to breast.
Lamouries, can I ask you a
question about something?
I'll think about it, but only if you
start calling me by my actual name.
Ugh.
Fine then, Lamas.
Yes, what is it?
Boxxo.
He's not a simple magic tool, is he?
Tell me, what exactly is
going on inside there?
Well, to tell you the truth, I'm not
really that sure what Boxxo is either.
But he understands what people say, and
he can even respond like he gets it.
To me, he's the same as a human.
I see.
So that's how you think of me.
Thank you, llamas.
I've heard enough.
I'll leave it there for today.
But one day, Boxo will belong to me.
Sooner or later, you'll open your
eyes to the greatness that is Zalori.
Uh-huh, if you say so.
Anyway, Boxo's not here now.
So head back home.
Fine, but I'll be back again.
Until then, I'll let you
continue taking care of him.
Make sure to polish him
up nice and shiny for me.
I don't know if it's just me,
but it seems Suori's been a
lot more talkative than before.
Hello there.
Guaxo, how long have you been there?
What were you doing?
You should have spoken up sooner.
Anyway, all sorts of stuff happened today.
Wanna hear about it? Hello there.
I'll see
you next time
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.